### **KATHERINE "KITTY" MOORE**

™ katherineelainemoore@gmail.com | ■ 416-937-5029 | ↑ Mississauga, ON Behance: kittyxemm | LinkedIn: Katherine Moore | Portfolio: https://kittyxemm.com

#### **SUMMARY**

Graphic artist and visual designer passionate about human-centric design, driven by complexity in need of simplification. 16 years of experience building with HTML and CSS including post-secondary education, and 3 years of experience designing for clients. An out-of-the-box thinker with a critical eye for improvement opportunities.

#### **SKILLS**

**Technical:** HTML, CSS, GitHub, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JQuery

**Software:** Figma, FigJam, VS Code, Brackets, Miro, Trello, Adobe CC (InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, etc.), Google Drive (including Docs, Sheets, Slides, etc.), FileZilla, Slack, Zoom **UX/UI Design Tools:** User insight, Interviewing for user experience, Persona creation, Affinity diagrams, Prioritization matrices, Storyboarding, User flow diagrams, Usability testing, Colour theory, Typography, Iconography, Atomic design, Heuristic evaluation, Competitor analyses, Composition and grids, Sitemapping, Wireframing, Prototyping

#### **PROJECTS**

#### **Journey to Diversity Workplaces** | https://kittyxemm.com/pages/j2dw

This project was intended to improve upon a non-profit organization's existing website. Tasks included creation of a new sitemap through card sorting, an interface overhaul, and usability tests to further determine user needs and priorities.

• **Skills & Technologies Used:** Stakeholder interview, User research (usability testing and surveys) & data analysis, Affinity diagram, Storyboarding, Sitemapping, Prototyping, Figma & FigJam, Slack, Zoom, Trello.

### **Indigenous Services Canada** | https://kittyxemm.com/pages/isc

By modernizing the look and feel of the Indigenous Services Canada pages on Canada.ca, this proposed redesign aims to better reflect and serve Indigenous cultures.

• **Skills & Technologies Used:** Heuristic evaluation, Usability testing, User interviews, Persona creation, Sitemapping, Interaction Design, Prototyping, Figma, Miro.

#### Pocket Closet | https://kittyxemm.com/pages/pocketcloset

An app that allows a user to "try on" outfits virtually for a mess- and stress-free experience while aiming to reduce needless spending and fast fashion.

• **Skills & Technologies Used:** User interviews and surveys, Data analysis, Persona Creation, Prototyping, User testing, Miro, Trello, Figma, Slack, Zoom, Adobe Illustrator.

#### RELEVANT WORK EXPERIENCE

#### Freelance artist and designer | Mississauga, Ontario | May 2017 - present

- Created custom designed artwork, graphics, logos, banners, and products in both digital and hands-on media.
- Instructed others to create various works of art with a variety of materials.

# **SpyderWorks, Inc.** | Mississauga, Ontario | September 2019 - October 2019 **Position held: Subcontracted interface designer**

- Assisted with wireframing for Solvable (Varsol and similar products) website.
- Collaborated with senior designers and stakeholders to discuss project iteration.

## **Lululemon** | Vancouver, British Columbia | May 2017 - September 2017 **Position held: Junior designer (contract)**

- Co-created rebranding proposal including mockups of app, website, and brand standards guide.
- Led company-wide effort to present more gender-inclusive branding.
- Suggested revisions to mockups reflecting in-store display techniques.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **Certificate in UX/UI**

University of Toronto March 2023

#### **Microcredential in Front-End Development**

Sheridan College August 2022

#### **Graphic Design and Visual Communication**

OCAD University September 2017

#### Advanced diploma in Visual and Creative Arts

Sheridan College

Graduated with Honours (85%+ average)

April 2017